Alright, some feedback on the custom merch site.
I input a picture of a dog on the couch. A customer wants this
engraved. this is what happened last night.
So, I know this is a different picture than the one I provided Steve.
This is just one I had. Ready to go on my laptop.
So, this is the default, without any changes.
Let me zoom out here so we can see everything in the video.
This is not going to engrave well. We're going to lose a ton of
detail here. It's just a lot of shading. A lot of white space.
If I increase contrast,
it puts us in the wrong direction.
If I lower contrast, we're not in any better shape.
We just lose, lose detail. rather than a contrast slider,
which I, which I understand, by the way, why we have a contrast slider,
I think there needs to be some level of, detail adjustment.
what I often do with chat GPT when I do this manually is ask
for less shading, ask it to outline more of the detail work,
just so it's more suitable for engraving. We're also not doing much to eliminate
background here, where we really just want to see the dog.
so that's something as well. this is the initial background image while it was
black and white, but the, the image wasn't full color when we started,
so yeah, I'd want to remove this background the best we can,
and just really highlight the, the main features of the subject instead of shade
the whole thing. if we go back.
Try
to do it this way. Okay.
This would engrave really well. I'd be happy with this.
so if I click Love It, Send to Print, it should generate a click
of work order.
Whoa,
fancy, we got SVGs now. Let's see if that worked.
don't mind my hand. This is an older, older endeavor.
Let's
see here. So, pull the SVG.
I think I can do this.
I'll just save it.
So,
let's
see.
This is interesting. The,
the SVGs I'm used to dealing with don't have a background like that,
but this appears to be giving me the correct settings,
so I'm wondering if it's a non-issue. this I'll have to investigate,
but, definitely a step in the right direction, for sure.
but yeah, that'll be my feedback for now.